<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="Ab_crunch_machine">AB CRUNCH ON MACHINE: break
		1. SIT ON MACHINE WITH
		YOUR FEET FIRMLY ON THE FOOT SUPPORT. break
		2. REST THE PADS AGAINST
		YOUR UPPER CHEST AND GRASP THE HAND HOLDS.
		break
		3. KEEP YOUR NECK IN
		NEUTRAL POSITION THROUGHOUT THE EXERCISE. break
		4. SLOWLY PULL FORWARD
		ON THE PADS TOWARDS YOUR THIGHS, CONTRACTING YOUR
		ABDOMEN. break
		5.
		SLOWLY RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION. break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1.
		ADJUST THE SEAT HEIGHT SUCH THAT THE PADS CONTACT YOUR UPPER
		CHEST.break
		2. DO NOT JERK OR MAKE SUDDEN MOVEMENTS.
	</string>
	<string name="Ab_crunch_with_Mediball">AB CRUNCH WITH MEDIBALL: break

		1. LIE ON YOUR BACK
		ON THE FLOOR WITH YOUR HIPS AND KNEES BENT AND FEET
		TOGETHER ON THE
		FLOOR. break
		2. LIFT YOUR HANDS VERTICALLY UP AGAINST THE CHEST AND
		HOLD THE
		MEDIBALL. break
		3. CURL YOUR UPPER TORSO UP TOWARDS YOUR KNEES
		WHILE THE ARMS KEPT
		STABLE, SO THAT ,THE MEDIBALL MOVES TOWARDS THE
		FOOT. break
		4. RAISE ONLY THE UPPER BACK UNTIL THE SHOULDER BLADES
		LOOSE CONTACT. DO
		NOT LIFT YOUR LOWER BACK. break
		5. SLOWLY LOWER
		YOURSELF TO THE STARTING POSITION. break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1. DO NOT
		JERK YOURSELF UP - SLOWLY BRING YOURSELF UP USING YOUR
		ABDOMINALS.
		break
		2. DO NOT LIFT YOUR LOWER BACK. break
	</string>

	<string name="Abdominal_bicycle">ABDOMINAL BICYCLE: break
		1. LIE ON THE FLOOR WITH
		BOTH YOUR HIPS AND KNEES AT 90 DEGREE ANGLES
		AND YOUR HEAD AND SHOULDER
		SLIGHTLY LIFTED OFF THE GROUND FINGERS
		TOUCHING THE SIDES OF YOUR HEAD.
		break
		2. PERFORM THE MOVEMENT BY CRUNCHING LEFT SIDE OF YOUR UPPER BODY
		AND
		BRINGING YOUR LEFT ELBOW AND RIGHT KNEE TOGETHER SIMULTANEOUSLY.
		break
		3. THIS ENDS UP MIMICKING A BICYCLING MOVEMENT IN LYING POSITION.
		break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1. MOVE IN A SLOW, CONTROLLED MANNER. break
	</string>

	<string name="Arm_swing_ab_crunch">ARM SWINGING AB CRUNCH: break

		1. LIE ON THE BACK,
		WITH KNEES BENT, FEET FLAT ON THE GROUND, AND HANDS
		STRAIGHT BEHIND THE
		HEAD. break
		2. EXHALE AND RAISE THE TORSO BY ROUNDING THE BACK AND
		REACH THE WRIST
		TO THE KNEE. break
		3. INHALE AND RETURN TO THE STARING
		POSITION. break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1. MAKE SLOW CONTROLLED MOVEMENTS.
		break
	</string>

	<string name="Back_Squats_Machine">BACK SQUATS ON MACHINE: break

		1. STAND UPRIGHT, FEET
		HIP WIDTH APART, HOLDING A BARBELL OR MACHINE ROD
		ACROSS THE BACK OF
		YOUR SHOULDERS, PALMS FORWARD. break
		2. SQUAT DOWN KEEPING YOUR SHINS
		PERPENDICULAR TO THE FLOOR UNTIL YOUR
		THIGHS ARE PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR.
		break
		3. LOOK FORWARD AND KEEP YOUR BACK STRAIGHT. break
		4. SLOWLY STAND
		UP TO THE STARTING POSITION. break

		KEY POINTS;
		1. DO NOT ALLOW YOUR
		KNEES TO MOVE TOO FAR FORWARD. break
		2. NEVER BOUNCE OR JERK. break
	</string>

	<string name="Benchpress_barbell">BENCH PRESS BARBELL: break
		1. LIE ON A BENCH WITH
		YOUR LEGS SLIGHTLY APART AND YOUR FEET ON THE
		FLOOR. break
		2. GRIP THE
		BARBELL WITH PALMS FACING UP AND ABOUT SHOULDER-WIDTH APART.
		break
		3.
		LIFT THE BARBELL TO THE START POSITION, YOUR ARMS FULLY EXTENDED.
		break
		4. SLOWLY LOWER THE BARBELL UNTIL IT TOUCHES YOUR CHEST, ELBOWS
		POINTING
		OUTWARD. break
		5. SLOWLY PRESS THE BARBELL TO THE STARTING
		POSITION. break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1. DO NOT ARCH YOUR BACK OR BOUNCE THE
		BAR OFF THE CHEST. break
		2. LET THE BAR DOWN IN A SLOW CONTROLLED
		MANNER. break
	</string>

	<string name="Bent_over_row">BENT OVER ROW WITH BARBELL: break
		1. STAND UPRIGHT
		WITH FEET SLIGHTLY WIDER THAN SHOULDER WIDTH APART.
		break
		2. HOLD THE
		BARBELL, BEND OVER YOUR WAIST WITH YOUR BACK STRAIGHT AND
		PARALLEL TO
		THE FLOOR. break
		3. KEEPING THE BACK STRAIGHT, PULL THE BARBELL TOWARDS
		YOUR LOWER CHEST.
		4. YOUR ELBOWS SHOULD BE POINTING UP TOWARDS THE
		CEILING. break
		5. SLOWLY RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION. break

		KEY
		POINTS: break
		1. DO NOT LET YOUR BACK ARCH OR MOVE UP AND DOWN. break
		2. KEEP BACK STRAIGHT AND PARALLEL TO THE FLOOR. break
		3. RAISE THE BAR
		UP AND DOWN IN A SLOW AND CONTROLLED MANNER. break
	</string>

	<string name="Bicep_curl_barbell">BICEP CURL BARBELL: break
		1. STAND WITH BACK
		STRAIGHT, FEET HIP-WIDTH APART, AND GRIP A BARBELL
		WITH AN UNDERHAND
		GRIP, PALMS FORWARD. break
		2. YOUR ARMS SHOULD BE DOWN AND THE BARBELL
		SHOULD BE ON YOUR UPPER
		THIGHS. break
		3. KEEPING YOUR ELBOWS CLOSE TO
		YOUR BODY, CURL THE BAR UP TO YOUR
		CHEST. break
		4. SLOWLY LOWER THE
		BARBELL TO THE STARTING POSITION. break

		KEY POINTS;
		1. DO NOT MOVE YOUR
		BODY IN AN ATTEMPT TO COMPLETE THE CURL. break
		2. DO NOT LET YOUR
		ELBOWS LEAVE YOUR SIDES. break
		3. LET THE BARBELL DOWN IN A SLOW,
		CONTROLLED MANNER. break
	</string>

	<string name="Bicep_curl_swissball">BICEP CURL ON SWISS BALL: break
		1. SIT WITH BACK
		STRAIGHT ON A SWISS BALL WITH FEET FIRMLY PLANTED ON
		THE FLOOR. break
		2. GRIP TWO DUMBBELLS WITH AN UNDERHAND GRIP, PALMS FORWARD. break
		3.
		YOUR ARMS SHOULD BE DOWN AND THE DUMBBELLS SHOULD BE ON YOUR UPPER
		THIGHS. break
		3. KEEPING YOUR ELBOWS CLOSE TO YOUR BODY, CURL THE
		DUMBBELLS UP TO YOUR
		CHEST. break
		4. SLOWLY LOWER THE DUMBBELLS TO THE
		STARTING POSITION. break

		KEY POINTS;
		1. DO NOT MOVE YOUR BODY OR SWING
		ON THE SWISS BALL. break
		2. DO NOT LET YOUR ELBOWS LEAVE YOUR SIDES.
		break
		3. LET THE DUMBBELLS DOWN IN A SLOW, CONTROLLED MANNER. break
	</string>

	<string name="Bicep_hammer_curls">BICEP HAMMER CURLS WITH DUMBBELLS: break

		1. STAND
		GRIPPING THE DUMBBELL IN EACH HAND WITH MID-PRONE POSITION.
		break
		2.
		LIFT FOREARM BY BENDING THE ELBOW. break
		3. RETURN TO THE STARTING
		POSITION. break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1. MAKE SLOW CONTROLLED MOVEMENTS.
		break
	</string>

	<string name="Bicep_stretch">BICEPS STRETCH: break
		1. STAND FACING A WALL. break
		2. PLACE THE WHOLE OF YOUR RIGHT ARM AN THE WALL AT SHOULDER HEIGHT -
		PALM SIDE TOUCHING IT AND FINGERS POINTING TO THE SIDE
		3. KEEP THE ARM
		IN POSITION, TURN YOUR BODY AWAY FROM THE WALL. break
		4. FEEL THE
		STRETCH IN YOUR RIGHT BICEPS AND STRETCH. break
		5. REPEAT BY SWITCHING
		SIDES. break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1. DO NOT BOUNCE OR JERK INTO THE
		STRETCH. break
		2. MAKE SLOW STEADY MOVEMENTS. break
		3. AVOID LOCKING
		JOINTS WHEN STRETCHING. break
		4. DO NOT LEAN FORWARD, KEEP CHEST UP.
		break
	</string>

	<string name="Breathing_squats">BREATHING SQUAT: break
		1. TAKE A COMFORTABLE STANCE
		WIDE ENOUGH TO SQUAT DOWN BETWEEN YOUR
		LEGS. break
		2. PLACE YOUR ARMS AT
		YOUR SIDES OR UP IN FRONT OF YOU AND INHALE. break
		3. EXHALE AS YOU
		LOWER YOURSELF DOWN. break
		4. GO AS LOW AS YOU COMFORTABLY CAN AND
		PAUSE. break
		5. INHALE AS YOU RETURN TO STANDING. break
		6. REPEAT AT THE
		PACE YOU NATURALLY BREATHE.
		break
		KEY POINTS: break
		1. BREATHE THROUGH
		YOUR NOSE. break
		2. IF YOU NEED TO EXHALE THROUGH YOUR MOUTH, KEEP A
		LITTLE TENSION IN
		YOUR LIPS. break

	</string>

	<string name="Butt_Blaster">BUTT BLASTER: break
		1. LIE FACE DOWN ON THE MACHINE
		AND PLACE ONE FOOT ON THE PEDAL. break
		2. GRASP THE HAND HOLD UNDER THE
		FRONT OF THE BACK. break
		3. SLOWLY EXTEND YOUR LEG AND PUSH THE PEDAL
		UP TOWARDS THE CEILING.
		break
		4. TIGHTEN YOUR GLUTES, HAMSTRINGS,
		QUADRICEPS TO GET FULL EFFECT OF
		EACH PRESS. break
		5. SLOWLY RETURN TO
		THE STARTING POSITION. break
		6. REPEAT ON THE OTHER LEG. break

		KEY
		POINTS: break
		1. AS YOUR BODY IS INVERTED, BLOOD RUSHES YOUR HEAD, SO
		BREATHE
		STEADILY. break
		2. DO NOT JERK OR MAKE SUDDEN MOVEMENTS. break
	</string>

	<string name="Chest_press_on_cable_machine">CABLE CHEST PRESS: break
		1. STAND WITH YOUR FEET HIP
		WIDTH WIDE. break
		2. REACH BACK AND GRASP THE STIRRUPS, PALMS FORWARD.
		break
		3. POSITION ELBOWS OUT TO SIDES, SLIGHTLY LOWER THAN SHOULDER
		HEIGHT.
		break
		4. POSITION HANDS SLIGHTLY NARROWER THAN ELBOW WIDTH IN
		FRONT OF UPPER
		ARMS. break
		5. PUSH STIRRUPS OUT STRAIGHT UNTIL ARMS ARE
		STRAIGHT
		. break
		6. RETURN STIRRUPS TO ORIGINAL POSITION. break

		KEY
		POINTS: break
		1.MAINTAIN GOOD SPINAL ALIGNMENT
		.break
	</string>

	<string name="Cable_Tri_pushdown">CABLE TRI PUSH DOWN: break
		1. STAND AT THE MACHINE,
		FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. break
		2. REACH UP AND GRASP THE HANDLE WITH
		BOTH THE HANDS, PALMS DOWN. break
		3. BRING THE HANDLE DOWN UNTIL YOUR
		ELBOWS ARE BY YOUR SIDE. break
		4. KEEPING THE ELBOWS AT A FIXED
		POSITION, MOVE YOUR HANDS UNTIL YOUR
		ARMS ARE ALMOST STRAIGHT. break
		5.
		SLOWLY RETURN TO THE STARTING POSITION. break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1. KEEP
		YOUR ELBOWS AND UPPER ARMS BY YOUR SIDE IN A FIXED POSITION AT
		ALL
		TIMES. break
		2. MAKE SLOW CONTROLLED MOVEMENTS. break
	</string>

	<string name="calf_raise_single_leg">CALF RAISE SINGLE LEG: break
		1. STAND URIGHT WITH
		ALL OF THE FEET FIRMLY ON THE FLOOR. break
		2. KEEP YOUR CHEST LIFTED,
		ABS TIGHT AND MAINTAIN A VERY SLIGHT FLEXION
		AT YOUR HIPS WITH A
		STRAIGHT LOW BACK. break
		3. HOLD THE WALL FOR SUPPORT IN FRONT. break
		4. SLOWLY PRESS THE BALL OF YOUR FEET ONTO THE FLOOR AND LIFT YOUR
		HEELS
		UP. break
		5. LOWER DOWN SLOWLY TO RETURN BACK TO THE STARTING
		POSITION WITHOUT
		STOPPING IN BETWEEN. break

		KEY POINTS: break

		1. DO NOT
		CHANGE YOUR HIP OR KNEE POSITION, ONLY ANKLE MOTION SHOULD BE
		ALLOWED.
		break
	</string>

	<string name="Cat_stretch">CAT STRETCH: break
		1. GET DOWN ON YOUR HANDS AND
		KNEES. break
		2. LET YOUR ABDOMEN AND BACK SLOWLY DROOP DOWNWARD,
		STRETCHING.
		3. HOLD THE POSITION FOR 10 SECONDS. break
		4. NEXT SLOWLY
		ARCH YOUR BACK UPWARD AS FAR AS POSSIBLE AND HOLD FOR 10
		SECONDS. break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1. DO NOT BOUNCE OR JERK INTO THE STRETCH. break
		2.
		MAKE SLOW STEADY MOVEMENTS. break
		3. AVOID LOCKING JOINTS WHEN
		STRETCHING. break
	</string>

	<string name="Chest_stretch">CHEST STRETCH: break
		1. STAND UPRIGHT WHILE FACING A
		DOORWAY OR CORNER. break
		2. PLACE FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART WITH RIGHT
		FOOT SLIGHTLY IN FRONT OF
		THE LEFT. break
		3. RAISE YOUR RIGHT ARM TO
		SHOULDER LEVEL AND PLACE FROM PALM TO ELBOW
		ON THE DOORFRAME OR WALL .
		break
		4. LEAN BODY FORWARD. break
		5. REPEAT ON OTHER SIDE. break

		KEY
		POINTS: break
		1. DO NOT BOUNCE OR JERK INTO THE STRETCH. break
		2. MAKE
		SLOW STEADY MOVEMENTS. break
		3. AVOID LOCKING JOINTS WHEN STRETCHING.
		break
	</string>

	<string name="Dead_lift">DEAD LIFT: break
		1. STAND HOLDING THE BARBELL WITH A
		WIDE GRIP AND FEET SHOULDER WIDTH
		APART. break
		2. LOWER THE BAR KEEPING
		CLOSE TO YOUR BODY AND MAINTAINING A SLIGHT
		BEND IN YOUR KNEES. break
		3. MAINTAIN A FLAT BACK THROUGH OUT AND KEEP THE SHOULDER BLADES
		PULLED
		BACK AND CHEST OUT. break
		4. RETURN TO STARTING POSITION
		. break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1. PUSH YOUR HIPS BACK DURING THE EXERCISE. break
	</string>
	<string name="Diagonal_lunges">DIAGONAL LUNGES: break
		1. STAND WITH FEET SHOULDER WIDTH APART. break
		2. USE YOUR RIGHT FOOT TO STEP FORWARD AT 45 DEGREES (HALF WAY BETWEEN
		12 AND 3 O’CLOCK POSITION OR 12 AND 9 O’CLOCK POSITION)
		3. KEEP HEAD AND EYES FORWARD, SHOULDERS AND PELVIS SQUARE TO THE FRONT
		4. ALLOW THE TRAILING LEG TO PIVOT NATURALLY AS YOU DROP INTO THE
		LUNGE. break
		5. RETURN TO START POSITION AND ALTERNATE BETWEEN LEGS. break

		KEY POINTS: break
		1. DO NOT TURN THE WHOLE BODY 45-DEGREES AND LUNGE. THIS WILL BE NO
		DIFFERENT THAN A FRONT LUNGE. break
		2. MAKE SLOW CONTROLLED MOVEMENTS. break
	</string>

</resources>