<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="metabolic_questions">
		<item>1. I sleep best:</item>
		<item>2. I sleep best if:</item>
		<item>3. I sleep best and wake up feeling most rested if I:</item>
		<item>4. After vigorous exercise, I tend to crave:</item>
		<item>5. In order to last 4 hours between meals and maintain mental
			clarity and a sense of well-being, I prefer to eat:
		</item>
		<item>6. Which best describes your reaction to sugar or sweet foods
			such
			as jelly donuts, candy or sweetened drinks:
		</item>
		<item>7. My body shape is closest to:</item>
		<item>8. Which statement best describes your disposition toward food
			in general:
		</item>
		<item>9. In general, I prefer:   </item>
		<item>10. Instinctually, I prefer to eat:</item>
		<item>11. Which list of fish most appeals to your taste without
			concern for calories or fat content:
		</item>
		<item>12. When eating dairy products, do you feel best after eating:
		</item>
		<item>13. With regard to snacking, do you:</item>
		<item>14. Which characteristics best describe you:</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="OPTION_A">
		<item>A. when I eat 1-2 hours before going to sleep</item>
		<item>A. my dinner is composed of mainly meat with some vegetables or
			other carbohydrates
		</item>
		<item>don’t eat sweet desserts like cakes, candy or cookies. If I eat
			rich dessert that is not overly sweet, such as high quality full fat
			ice cream, I tend to sleep okay.
		</item>
		<item>A. foods or drinks with higher protein and/or fat content such
			as a bodybuilder’s high-protein shake
		</item>
		<item>A. a meal predominately meat based, high in protein and fat
			(such as roast beef, pork, salmon…) with a carbohydrate as a
			supplement to the meal
		</item>
		<item>A. I get a rush of energy, may get the jitters or may feel good
			for a short time but then I am likely to have a blood sugar crash,
			resulting in the need for more of the same or having to eat some real
			food to normalize myself.
		</item>
		<item>A. Mesamorphic or “V” shaped, like a typical wrestler, gymnast
			or weight lifter type; Endomorphic or more naturally round shape but
			I am naturally quite strong and respond very well to anaerobic sports
			or strength training type exercises.
		</item>
		<item>A. I love food and live to eat!</item>
		<item>A. to salt my foods most of the time</item>
		<item>A. dark meat, such as the chicken or turkey legs and thighs over
			the white breast meat
		</item>
		<item>A. anchovy, caviar, herring, mussels, sardines, abalone, clams,
			crab, crayfish, lobster, mackerel, octopus, oyster, salmon, scallops,
			shrimp, snail, squid, tune (dark meat)
		</item>
		<item>A. richer, full fat yogurts and cheeses or desserts</item>
		<item>A. tend to do better with snacks between meals</item>
		<item>A. creative, digest food well in general, have a strong immune
			system and don’t get sick often, have an appetite for proteins, feel
			good when eating fats or fatty foods, more muscular or inclined to
			gain muscle and/or strength easily
		</item>
	</string-array>
	<string-array name="OPTION_B">
		<item>B. when I eat as much as 3 or 4 hours before going to sleep
		</item>
		<item>B. my dinner is composed mainly of vegetables or other
			carbohydrates and a comparatively small serving of meat
		</item>
		<item>B. even if I should eat a sweet dessert now and then</item>
		<item>B. foods or drinks higher in carbohydrate (sweetener), such as
			Gatorade, soda, or fruit juice
		</item>
		<item>B. a meal predominately carbohydrate based, such as a salad or
			vegetables with some bread, and a small amount of protein
		</item>
		<item>B. I can do quite well on sweet things and I don’t seem to be
			negatively affected, even though I know that too much is not good for
			me.
		</item>
		<item>B. Ectomorphic or long and lean like a rower or triathlete;
			Endomorphic or more naturally round shaped but I respond better to
			endurance athletics than to strength training or anaerobic sports.
		</item>
		<item>B. I am not fussed over food in general and I eat to live in
			general.</item>
		<item>B. to taste my foods and apply salt once in a while, but am not
			particularly attracted to salty foods</item>
		<item>B. light meat such as the chicken or turkey breast over the dark
			leg and thigh meat</item>
		<item>B. light fish, catfish, cod, flounder, haddock, perch, scrod,
			sole, trout, tune (white), turbot</item>
		<item>B. lighter low fat yogurt and cheeses or desserts</item>
		<item>B. tend to last between meals easily in general</item>
		<item>B. logical, more lithe of build, tend to be sensitive to
			temperature changes and flu season and wouldn’t really consider your
			immune system one of your stronger attributes, prefer light meats and
			lower fat foods, are more inclined toward endurance athletics</item>
	</string-array>
</resources> 